Yes, ma'am.
Good evening.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
Tomorrow is another day for us, Shuui and Irshuugarasu.
So today...
I know, Matt, it's 9:00 p.m.
Our newest
Our newest single.
Our newest song.
Blues Dizziness.
The music video for it will be released at 9:00 p.m.
We'd like to do the distribution just before that.
The make-up members are Hoshino, Kobayashi, Nakayama, Kunimo and Kanami.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
We'd like you to upload your stories as well.
I'm going to make a comment that we're going to open YouTube now, and I'm going to try to make a comment that we're going to open YouTube now.
Let's go around one more time.
I don't know.
I really don't know.
We're working on it, so you'll have to wait a little bit.
He's mumbling.
Hold on.
Hold on a second.
Yes, sir.
Female.
Female medium.
Something that started
Something.
What's going on?
what?
Um...
I'm getting ready to go to the bathroom.
All women.
Inside a woman.
Female medium
It has begun.
Great great great great.
Challenging.
Mr. Kobayashi from.
I wonder. I wonder if it's done.
Did you hear that?
I naturally become silent too.
If I hear you, I'll turn silent.
Can you hear me?
Do you hear me?
It's getting better.
He says he's getting better.
You hear that, doctor?
Okay!
Let's get a closer look from us, shall we? Let's have a look!
Well, since we're here...
Actually, we couldn't hear you, so we'd like to apologize and give you a closer look.
We'll give you a closer look. Okay, we're out!
I don't know what's going on, but next time...
He's a nice guy, isn't he?
I'm the best at what I do.
Yes, by listening to it.
Yes, yes.
But also, I don't know why
Because he's not the same person.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, I see, that's the
That's the best story, I'll tell you.
I see.
Mirei, isn't it awful that you cut your hair?
And this is a week and three weeks old.
Yes, it is.
Actually, it's a snack, too. When it's peeled off...
I can't hear anything.
Can you come a little closer?
We all have to come in.
No, we're not.
Oh, my God.
What have you got on you?
You want me to put this up?
Let's try the switch delivery.
Switch.
What?
You want me to put this up?
Again, again, there may be no sound.
Once again, then, it could be because the recorder is close.
Sure thing.
If you move the desk closer to the camera, people won't be able to get in.
Want to try moving it just a little bit closer?
Yes, I think so. Just a little bit closer.
I think it's going to work.
I got something.
Oh, again.
It's a character generator. Oh, I see it.
Hang in there.
It's your match. Yes, it is. No, it's not. I'm gonna go for it.
Donkey? Trap?
You got it? Come on.
Thank you for watching.
ASM squid for food.
This is Afren.
Lunon ASM.
Eee?
Good luck, Mr. Woo.
How's that?
That's Goala's ini.
no aces out
How does it look?
I understand.
I'm sorry.
Go for it.
Mr. Nonaka.
How is it?
I'm soaked in water and fire.
I'm done soaking candy in water over an open fire.
Mike, Mike, Mike...
I'm sure it picks up all the noises of everyday life.
I'm having fun. The prince says he's doing a great job.
He says he's doing a great job.
I'll talk to him. - Okay, stop it. Let him lean back.
Let's not do that, let's just lean back and let him do his thing.
Can you hear me? Kukwinu here.
Kukwinu! Who's there?
Who's there?
It's a bird!
Who's this? - It's a bird, sir!
What's going on?
I've set the sound settings to "simple, simple, simple" and there's a setting for this...
I'm in the middle of this...
It's in there.
I wonder what it is... sensor
It's stuck!
I'm not sure if it's the NETBIKE, but it's already in front of me, and I'm not delivering it.
is razор
This is a lion.
Hey.
How's it going?
Can you hear me?
It's good.
Can you hear me? Can you hear everyone?
What do you think?
Can you hear me?
It's not working. It's all jammed up.
Everybody's jammed up.
I can hear you just fine.
Oh, so everyone's stuffed.
Here you go again.
Good evening, everyone.
It's Sayumi Asano. We are Shutes F6.
Today, we will be premiering the music video for "Blue Dizziness" that was released today.
The music video for Blue Dizziness will be released later today at 9:00 p.m., so we'd like to do a special distribution right before that.
Yay!
Shina and
Kobayashi
Yokomoto
This is Kazami.
I'd like to send you a message.
Shina
So...
Blue Dizzinness
This is the course.
It's Blue Dizziness, right?
I like sweets and things at the desk.
Blue Blue Bee is Indigo bound, Indigo bound, or rather, if you want to do just that, there are blue snacks...
I know it sounds like I'm wasting my time here, but, Mr. Shoulder Lifter, I'm just gonna pick one.
I'm going to pick one up while I'm on the pepper moon.
There's also yogurt.
I'm not sure if it's a little pink in the chiffre or if it's a little blue in the yogurt...
I'm glad to see that the adults and former faculty members are so lively and active.
I'm glad you're here!
I can't hear this once
I can't hear this once...
Akiki, let's put it in the middle.
I'll speak up.
I don't know.
If you can hear me, I'll be running soon.
If you hear it, it's the recorder.
I'm eating.
I don't know.
Mr. Tomo.
Mr. Illumipi, I think he's just going to end up eating a candy bar.
I heard that.
That's good.
So, what do you guys think after seeing the blue Dizziness in action?
I know it's a little abbreviated, but what did you think of it when you first got it?
What was your impression when you first got it?
Summer Critter... the new song that was released in the summer... was like that.
I couldn't imagine what the next song would be like.
I wondered what kind of route you were going to take.
It's really cool.
It's cool, isn't it?
I'm just thinking it's a bit of a challenge.
Like, "Can we sing this? Like, "Can we sing this?
It's really cool.
We're really going to have more songs than we've ever had before.
I guess so.
What about Yu? Let's hear it later. What about you, Nanaka?
When I saw the lyrics, I could relate to a lot of them.
I thought it was very understandable.
I usually listen to a lot of kpop.
I've never really had this kind of music before, but it has an atmosphere a little closer to today's kpop, a little between girlishness and maturity.
It's a little bit between girlishness and maturity, and it fits with the members' generation, and I think it fits with the way we are as a group right now.
That's right.
The rap part was really cool.
It's so cool.
There are so many rap parts in the song.
You've been traveling a lot lately, haven't you?
Yes, I do.
There's been more, that's for sure.
It's refreshing.
Yeah, yeah.
We performed for the first time at the Shimo-Pla festival.
At that time, I thought we were able to create a different atmosphere from the other Stardust idols' songs.
I thought I was able to create a different atmosphere from the other Stardust idols' songs.
I see.
Yes, I'm sure there are a lot of people who are surprised by it.
I'm sure there are a lot of people who are surprised by this song.
I hope we can create a chance for people to fall in love with this song.
And Yu?
Yu-san, when I first played it...
I played "Blue Dizziness" for the first time.
Why do you call it blue?
When I saw the title
I thought it was really Blue Dizziness.
Did you know what Blue Dizziness meant?
I didn't know that.
I didn't know that, but when I heard the song, I thought "Blue" sounded really good.
I thought it was so cool!
The worldview of Blue Dizziness is like the instability of adolescence.
I think the world of Blue Dizziness is about the instability of adolescence, about impatience and conflict, about not being able to find the right answer, and about not trying to break out of your shell.
It's like you're trying to break out of your shell.
It's like they're trying to grasp something.
It's like the worldview really sticks with you.
I get it.
I was wondering about your comment.
Did you use it for a role?
There's a guy who's playing a role.
It says "broody.
Burdi?
What kind of burdies do you like?
Only if it's a burdi.
Blue eyes?
Like blue eyes.
Blue eyes.
I can say "dj", "new rude dinus", "burdi", "burdigier"...
Bourdie is not short for "Bourdie." Bourdie, it's "Bulgarian yogurt.
I'm listening to Komena's music!
We have a teacher who can translate the lyrics.
What about him?
Mr. Yasumoto.
He's on the edge.
He's a bit on the edge.
What? Really?
He's always trying to push the line between there and there.
It's a habit of mine. I can't help it.
The members still call it Blue Dizziness.
This song itself was performed at the Stapla festival and Chuo University's school festival.
I haven't colored it yet.
That's true.
I think Blue Dizziness is fine.
I'll see what I can do.
Well, I'll ask our government doc.
See what our official has to say about it.
He's a bit...
Yes, I see.
What do you think of the blue Dizziness?
What do you think?
I've asked Chiaki Sato of Mushroom Kingdom to write the lyrics.
I've asked her to write the lyrics for a trilogy.
The first one is Buddha Dizzy's
I wonder how the trilogy will turn out.
I'm sure this will be another point of enjoyment.
But here it is
What is it?
The second part of the trilogy is coming!
It's been decided!
I snagged it!
I snagged it, didn't I?
I gagged on it!
What's the title, then?
Are you sure about this? You're writing the title?
It's fine.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I don't know what you're talking about.
What about the second one?
How about a two-parter?
Ristaldrup.
Uh...
I heard you.
Why?
What?
I think it's a Christmas sung-along.
It's a Christmas sung-along.
It's a winter song, isn't it?
Natsu Kyuwha is released every year, so there are a lot of songs that are released every year, but it's a winter song
winter songs winter songs winter clothes this is also really crystal gallop and that too
I hope you will enjoy the winter songs and the crystal gallops.
I hope you'll be able to enjoy the show today.
I found a riddle on the Blue Dizziness box on the mx website.
Is it okay if I turn blue?
I'm sorry if I'm turning blue, but I thought someone else had taken over the site, and at first I thought it wasn't sex, but then I was too scared to look for it, and when I found the sundress, I thought it might be too difficult.
I'm sorry if it was too difficult when I found the sundress, but it's difficult.
First of all...
This... this... this... how about this?
It took me an hour to find it, but I was able to do it in an hour.
This is the maze. What does it say?
If you follow this maze, you'll see the word
If you follow this maze, you'll see the word "When".
It's the title of our album.
Now.
Indigo?
The album title, then. Shall we all do it together?
Okay.
Ready?
Indigo Hour.
So, this is Indigo Hour.
We were planning to tell you the title of the album before it's released in February.
It was so difficult, wasn't it?
This maze is so difficult that you can't get there?
I couldn't get there.
I got a lot of compliments on my hard work.
You did great! You did great! You did great!
Where do you want me to get Indigo's reading from? I mean, the background is indigo blue, so...
Bubbles on the Indigo.
It's very difficult.
I think it's difficult. Yes, Indigo doesn't come up very often.
Indigo doesn't come up very often, because we don't usually read it.
I could solve the email, but I could never figure out the Indigo.
I did see the color Indigo in the icon header.
But it's been a while now, since the Summer Glitter show.
I hope you're enjoying it.
I wonder...
Some people say the maze was a "you".
Really?
Isn't that amazing?
Even if you knew something about the maze... the maze... the maze...
They don't even know what it is.
The moment you see this, you're like...
It's like a dead end.
It's hard
It's hard...
Then why did you go on?
That's not it.
It's like...
I could have done it first.
It's so clear, so clear!
It's mine.
Thank you very much.
I'm trying to solve a riddle.
Does the shape of the book mean anything to you?
Do they?
Now this one is stylish.
Stylish.
But you know what?
All this time...
Wait.
Hull Prize.
Come on.
Two letters in a name.
You've always had a two letter name.
When you think about it...
It's true...
Indigo.
Indigo Hour...
What's the English word?
It's when you get to the English letters.
I was on Music Arts
Music Arts again.
There was a playlist.
I was wondering what's going to happen when they come back with the 4 Earth's and stuff.
I wonder if it's going to be in Nakayama, where the water is... where the water is.
I'm thinking right away, if not now, I can make it, Kobayashi can make it.
I'm sure it'll work, Kokubun.
I said "Kokubu" and you said 4 of them are different, so what do you mean they're not the same?
The log page has changed a lot since yesterday.
Today's 12:00 is the 12th hour of the character!
The next album is Kobayashi & Nakayama.
Kobayashi and Nakayama.
That's funny.
It's so funny, it's been canceled.
And the costumes.
First of all, Arthur's changed.
What happened?
You look like you've been dazzled.
Did he?
That was a real mess.
Actually, on the day of the music video that's going to be shown later.
Arthur and I shot it together.
It was a beautiful sunny day, which is rare for us.
Recently.
It was amazing.
It's very rare when we shoot outside.
There wasn't a cloud in the sky.
I was the first one on the tennis court. I was Cocona.
Right next to me. Right next to you? Right when I lifted it up, it was right here. It's annoying. The sun is annoying.
I mean, it's the best time, but it's the best time, but it's so shaky, it's a big fight.
I mean, me and Cocona, we look a little bit scary, but we're so dazzling in the field, you know, looking at the sun.
I couldn't stand up. I couldn't stand up.
I didn't get a chance to get in there today, so I did it myself.
That's right.
They're calling him "Kobayashi Nakayama" and forgetting "Mayama
Oh, that's right, they kept saying "Mayama
I forgot "Kobayashi, Nakayama" I picked it up for fun
You did pretty well, didn't you?
I told Riko earlier...
We have bicycles and kickboards, right?
You know, the way they all stop wearing gold?
Or the way your shoulders look when you're on the bike.
You know that, right?
I know.
I was on a kickboard.
I was on a kickboard, and I was the only one with a really long neck.
Why does that bother you? You'll see later.
Let's see.
Yeah, it's long.
I cut it when we were together.
That's right.
That part's probably...
It's longer than everyone else's.
Longer than they are.
My neck's longer.
My neck is really long.
But, you know, I'm trying to straighten my posture on the kickboard.
And behind him...
Maybe Yuna.
Yuna and Kana are on the stage.
So his neck got even longer.
It was hilarious. It was hilarious.
Where is that?
Is it official? Official XXS.
It has the same look as the one from the XS.
It's got a long neck! I mean...
Yeah! Yeah, it stands up too much. It kind of stands up too much.
It's just...
Maybe Yuna is desperate.
Actually, I can't ride a bike.
You're lying!
So we're like kickboarding on a mat. But...
I've never even ridden a kickboard before. I was so scared at first.
We shot it in the evening at first, and then in the middle of the second half.
In terms of the music video we shot...
I should have just left Mire-chan out of it.
I asked her to share.
I liked the dash better at first, but it turned out to be super exhilarating.
But the next day, my muscles were sore.
I think I was scared.
I was pushing it.
He was pushing himself too hard.
Mire-chan would rather take a cab than a bike.
Let's put it on the cab.
It won't show.
I haven't ridden a bike for a while, so I can't ride a bike.
We were on a train.
We didn't see each other.
It's getting noisy.
That's true.
I won't put a hojo ring on it.
Hoju-ring.
One hojerin in a very fancy place.
Rattle rattle rattle.
Even I wore a hojyurin till I was about five.
What, like that? That's how it was, I guess.
I don't understand what this book means.
Really? It's new.
The music video will be released at 9:00 p.m.
Oh, I think he'll be in it. What?
What? Shhhhhh?
You're going to do it?
Come on.
The camera.
He was the cameraman from our old drama.
So I thought, "Oh, no, it's been a long time.
So I thought, "It's been a long time." And then I got all emo about it.
Kimi Sora? Yes, there was a drama called Kimi Sora.
And he did the voice of Sabo-san, who was in Kimisora.
He's doing it.
He got married. It's all over the news.
We're actually a band.
I miss Kimisora... it was so long ago.
I think it's been a year...
It was just a coincidence, but it made me really happy.
I was so happy... and there were people I hadn't seen in a long time... who were talking with us...
Yes.
Yes, it's been a long time.
It's been a long time.
I don't know if it's okay if I say a little bit more about the story since the mv is going to be distributed here, but I'd like to talk about the story behind the story, or something like that.
I don't know if it's okay to say something about the story behind the scene or what happened during the scene.
I'm wondering if it's okay to tell some more stories now that the mv is going to be distributed.
What?
Uh...
Something memorable?
It's a network.
I'll be networked.
I know, I can't tell you anymore.
It's going to be a network.
There it is.
Oh, I... I...
I was, um...
Overseas.
I was...
I was doing...
Sometimes I have to press something.
It's pretty difficult.
Oh, you were doing your best.
You'll see what was so hard to press.
We'll see what happens in the next 30 minutes.
You're pretty slow.
Different people?
Yeah, I guess.
No, it's people.
It's like, "Okay, okay.
It's kind of cool.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because I was...
I had oden at the convenience store on the way home.
Oh, yeah, it was pretty much gone.
I'm sure it was...
We finished shooting around 6:00 p.m., but the sun was setting early.
I wish I was shooting on the flat side of the mountain, but I was surrounded by mountains, so the sun set pretty early.
I was shooting in the mountains surrounded by mountains, so the sun set pretty early because the mountains were so high, and it was cold.
I was cold.
I couldn't pick up the voices, so I didn't end up spoiling the film.
It was okay.
I was fine. Just when I was talking to him, he spoiled it for me.
It's good. Which one should we eat next?
I'm going to sleep...
Yay! I'm having a snack tactic all by myself!
Let's drink water. We'll have a pot-a-potty party next time.
I'm buying oden at home.
I'm buying oden at home for the next pot-a-potty party.
I had pizza. - You just had pizza.
Yes, I went with my mom.
He went to eat with his mom.
I was at the dentist's just now
Yoo's out.
She went to the dentist, then she went to bed, then she went to bed.
Are you okay?
Can I talk to you about the last three weeks?
You'll be fine.
It's fine.
There's still some time before the delivery, so I thought I'd give you an idea of what to expect.
So, Yu...
You were talking about how you went to get a cavity filled.
Yeah, but...
Three weeks, three months? Three weeks?
She said they didn't get all the way to the back.
He says the delivery was bad.
I was told the same thing, and I said no, no, no, no, I'm just taking advantage of the stable period to eat.
But I ended up going today, and the result was that the scammer was so amazing.
He took the scammer by his fingernails.
Wooooooo!
You saw that?
Did you see that?
Oh, my God, I can see that.
I'm gonna go get a minute with the con man.
I'll be right back.
Eeeeeeeee!
A checkup is just that, everyone's checkup.
And I can't forget my own definition of it, either.
Ehhhh!
Fireworks aren't that pretty.
Fireworks are beautiful, and they're all in order on the bus.
Grinding your teeth...
Ehhhh!
That's amazing.
You don't know because you're conscious.
I don't know, it's funny.
She said I should grind my teeth and keep doing it.
Eeeeeeeee!
Is that possible?
If you go to your reflexes, you'll see it.
Yes, sir.
I'm looking forward to the last issue.
No matter what I write...
I'm not going to do it.
I'm itching to see it now, too.
Is this it? I don't know.
It's a pine tree.
Is it this way?
Can I put the second one in first?
Sure.
What is this?
This way.
Here you go.
And, what do you call the fan club's 10th anniversary album? This is Memorial Books?
It's the Black Tiger 10th Anniversary Memorial Book.
I haven't seen it yet, so I'd like to take a look at it here.
This is the same as when the fan club started up.
Some of the members are in the same poses as when the fan club started up.
You can see the hairstyles, the poses, and so on, and it's pretty much the same.
That's something that the fan club can do.
I knew them all so well, so I came to the fan club.
Become a member of the secret society Black Tiger.
How do I change it?
I'll come in and do it.
Oh, my God.
Some people actually do this.
It's amazing.
With your own hands.
Let's just take a picture of your face taken at this time and run away and use it as a photo ID for AKN.
Don't do it! Don't do it!
Stop it!
At that time, at that time, when I suddenly debuted...
Why did you read about the hotel?
Wait...
I was looking at the "Suddenly" album when we actually entered.
So it's not really school-like, like it's not fun, like you want to be a part of it.
I took the photos at Fords, right?
I took the main photo, and then I cut the rest of the photos, and I did something similar to that, too.
I'm glad you're doing this.
What are you doing?
My cut... we shot it with about four people.
It's like the end, the end.
Okay, I'm done.
That's why we did it.
It's nice to be filmed.
You look like you're having fun.
It's really good.
This girl...
I was shooting this combination, and then in this one, it's like this girl, that girl, and this girl.
But, you know... this way.
You guys won't work on it.
No, they don't.
I found a commemorative book that commemorates the founding of the fan club, so I was looking at it.
I was looking at it, and I saw a conversation between Uchi, the assistant homeroom teacher, and Michiuchi, the manager at that time.
And there was a conversation between Uchi, the assistant homeroom teacher, and Michi, the manager at the time.
Now I'm wondering why the manager was having the conversation by himself.
He said he had to leave at a moment's notice.
Then Uchi's words of wisdom came up.
He said, "Voice is...
He said, "Voice is fun.
It's important, Michitaro.
What's up with that?
I'm just asking.
Yes, it's like something. Coffee. Coffee? Just tell me.
Coffee? Cafe au lait? Was it coffee?
Uh, yeah, it's like coffee. Coffee is like coffee. Coffee is like coffee.
Sweet Capellate. I want to say sweet Capellate. I want to say something like spoiled Capellate. What kind of thing are you talking about?
You know, if you have a copy, you can see it now, right?
I have a copy at home. I was involved with another group this time.
Yes, there it is, at the end.
The person who made this one was the same person who made the other one back then,
When I compared them, I found that Utsuchi-san was the best at making it an idol.
How come, Utsuchi-san was able to put a ribbon on his head?
Love and coffee are similar. It's important like this.
My favorite type of story is Utsuchi-sensei's shooting pictures,
Hiroyuki, I love the way he looks in his glasses and suit, though he looks goofy!
Really?
Yes, I love the firmer look, like a woo-hoo!
If I trace it back to coffee, it's black, but it's so strong, I'd like to put milk in it!
Sap and milk! Your name and coffee are similar!
What books do you have left?
But this new book doesn't have any of Mane-chan's quotes in it,
But there are a lot of us in the new book,
If we hear from you all, maybe it will be presented,
So, please join our fan club,
If you are a member of our fan club, please continue to patronize us.
If you are still wondering, please continue to patronize us.
Either way, please patronize us.
Please patronize us.
I'm good.
Sound changes, shy.
Already, if it's a blast, then we'll come over, and then we'll come over to the site, you know,
You guys are great.
They wrote a song for us,
I want to do this, and one day, I want to do it for Ebitua,
I'd like to offer my own songs to Ebitua someday.
Saki Yoshikawa, Furtime, that's interesting.
So this is blue, too. It is indeed.
How can I get it? The way to get it is to join a franchise.
We are waiting for you to join our secret society, Black Tiger.
If you join before then, you can still get it in time.
FC event?
That's right. That,
If you join the fan club, if you join the fan club. Then, what a surprise, it's a fan club only event,
You can participate in the event by yourself.
This is a live concert, on February 23rd, 2008, in Yokohama, Japan,
at the National Grand Hall,
I'm sure some of you may be wondering what a practical training is,
In the past, we used to call the performances produced by the members "practical training,
This time, we had Himato-chan and her sister members,
This time, the members of Himato-chan and her sister members will perform what they came up with at Cireb in a single live performance,
I see.
So, you are saying that you can see a live performance that you are going to produce.
That's right.
It's really good.
Everything is expensive, isn't it? And then, "Oh, my God! Oh my God!
It's late, so dream on. If you are a C subscriber, we'll be sending them out by January,
C, we'll be sending them out by January. This one, this one, this one?
Live shows are an advantage, though,
We'll be sending them out for free in January,
Please look forward to it.
Enjoy.
I'm looking forward to it.
Today,
Is it true?
Are you sure?
Oh, no,
It's rice.
It's good.
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
Eat it.
I like it.
Oh, my God,
What is it?
It'll be fun.
Yeah, it is.
It's a cancrum.
I'd like to keep track of it,
I'd like to keep track of it.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much for watching.
We have the FUFUC event coming up, but before that, we have a big arts and crafts show at Pialina MM on January 6 and 7.
How do you want it to be?
Well, it's the New Year, so I want it to be festive, but since it's at the piarina, I want to entertain even the people in the back of the hall.
There will be a performance like that, and the bon dance of the bon dance.
Congratulations, the seats are soft.
Really, the three of us will do it.
How I love it.
Really.
I recently had the opportunity to attend the 50th anniversary concert,
I recently had the opportunity to attend the 50th anniversary concert, and when I went to see other artists, the sound was great.
The sound was great.
I could see every part of the sound clearly.
Even if you look at where he draws, you can see it pretty well.
I'm sure.
You are doing one eri a day, I feel.
Yes, it's different.
You are doing it. Yes, I'm doing one a day for the live performance. Each member is in charge of one area a day,
Each member is in charge of a certain area, and each member is asked to do something today.
Yes, you can enhance the excitement. Please raise the excitement.
We will be asking each member to make a mentions and tag everyone, so please do it often.
Let's raise the excitement to all the members. I hope you will do it.
Many of you are doing this. One day at a time.
From the beginning, Rika-chan squats 30 times.
Hard. Hard from the first day.
I wonder if it's my class.
Tomorrow's class.
It was me today.
Did you do it?
Did you scream MT?
Can I ask you to shout now while you're resting?
At home? If not at home, can I watch it outside?
You know "Shouting Love in the Center of the World", right?
Is it known all over the world?
It's like a drama or something.
Cammade?
Aah!
Sorry, this has nothing to do with that. It's a true story.
Shout it out. Let's shout it, like in the streets.
You can ask for this. Really?
Shout it out. Thank you very much.
Okay, I'll do it. We've got 10 minutes. Let's go lie down and have a conversation.
Let's go lie down and have a conversation.
You all knew something today, but I don't know what it is, so it's not funny.
But it's only the third one. You've eaten three.
It's a magazine battleship, after all. Magazine Gunkan, I have something very relevant to say.
Yes, yes, let's chat until 5:09, 5:08.
We'll chat until 5:08, then scout down at 5:09.
You're going to raise the bar pretty close to 5:00? Yes. We're just barely ahead of the others.
But we can do anything atomatic. Yonezuזה's battlefield.
Like the Kragana people we had recently.
fixed amount year member yesterday.
Because I was a little bored after yesterday's lesson.
So we went out to dinner with the fixed-year members.
And we talked about Santa Claus.
Cocona has been leaving rice crackers for Santa since she was a little girl.
Cocona has been leaving crackers for Santa since she was a little girl.
But he ran out of them and didn't ask for them.
I even prepared a bag of crackers to give to him.
Crackers.
You all said that since everyone else was eating these, that coffee or something would be better, and I said, "Well, I guess it's a good thing we're not all eating coffee.
Come on, it's not a good thing.
We never ate any of them and cried every time we went to the yo-kart
Yuna used to write us a dubbed letter every year, but it got messy and she wrote it in katakana at the end.
Yuna was a good girl this year, she was great!
It's hard to read.
How old were you? Are you still coming?
I'm not here. I'm a student.
Elementary school?
Yeah, I guess so.
What was the last one?
Oh, I don't know.
That was me. A braceboard.
You know, like a skateboard.
It would have been so much fun to have one that went like this.
You got that one at the end.
Thank you. I'm so glad you gave it to me.
There was one time when you didn't come to Shouyou.
Why?
He didn't come. He didn't come.
Sometimes the time came, and you worked hard that year, and the next year you came.
That's right, next door.
I didn't tell anyone what I wanted.
It means they didn't get the message.
Words matter.
You never say them out loud.
Words, words.
And the last one is only one... five ships... push belt...
I'm not bringing it.
Oh, wait, wait.
And they're not coming, they're not coming anymore.
Our family, the Kobayashi family, is already..,
Santa's contract is over.
Mom told me seriously.
She told me.
Because the contract is over,
She said he wouldn't be coming.
She said the contract was over, but..,
But she came.
Then I thought I did it,
I was lucky and opened the bag,
It's a cat-back brace.
I don't want it. I don't want it.
What do you think?
I don't know.
It doesn't sound good.
The sound is bad.
I heard a sound the other day.
I need you to do something about it. I need you to listen.
Are you listening?
The deal was done.
Thank you.
Why didn't you finish your drink?
Because every year Santa Claus comes out on the 24th and once on the 22nd.
Oh, that one. What year is it?
Not inside the house, but outside the front door.
I knew that too.
It's a style that doesn't come inside.
It's regional, isn't it?
Nagoya is on the 22nd.
By the way, it's like an urban legend,
There was no rumor of Black Santa.
There was a lot of rumors.
What was it? In my area, they leave charcoal. It's not good.
If a child did something bad, his father would come and leave the charcoal in Kuromoto.
It's not nice. He is very humble.
If Papa were here, it would be popular.
When I was a little girl, I was about 22 years old, and I was sleeping before Christmas, and I heard the sound of a clang clang clang.
What? What happened?
Well, I was so scared that I hugged my mom.
She was like... she was so firm.
She's firm.
You're so strong.
She's firm. She's firm.
It's been a week. That's good.
That's good.
Can I get a plus on that?
We're going to different places, different years, different plans for the two of us, like a treasure hunt. We've been looking for a lot of stuff.
Yeah, that's great.
It's true.
I've been wanting one.
It's Christmas.
I want Santa to come.
Hey, I want Santa to come.
I want him to come.
I don't really understand how Christmas works.
He got me a Christmas tree, just in case,
I didn't understand much about presents,
It comes with money as well as ornaments.
It's difficult as it is.
A voice that has done a lot of work.
Once when I was little, an old man I didn't know dressed up as Santa and brought sweets to my house.
Next time.
I would like to ask for your understanding about those people.
I'm afraid that if I start to hear them, I'm going to have a very
moment, sure, I'll be 59 years old and I won't be able to hear them.
Hey, sure, it was five minutes ago.
They say they can hear you when you laugh.
The time I want you to hear me the most is when I'm in a good mood.
Can you hear me?
Are you okay?
I don't know.
Is it up a little bit?
I guess if I talk alone, it's just noise.
Wow.
That's sad.
Laughing to myself.
Ha-ha-ha.
A-ha-ha
Ha-ha-ha!
A-ha! That's hard!
You want to do it?
Well, here's the thing,
I would like to explain something.
Yes, on February 28th of next year, I will be releasing my 8th full-length album, 12-6,
I will be releasing my eighth full-length album
Unigoa, my eighth full-length album, which will be released on February 28th.
And today,
Blue Dizziness, which has been distributed in advance,
You can listen to it on various Tubutubu sites. The music video will be released at a premium starting at 9:00 p.m,
I hope you will all stand by for 9:00 p.m. Please stand by for the music video at 9:00 p.m.
Please wait for 9:00 p.m.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
It's a Saturday project, guys.
Indeed.
It was today earlier.
Well, let's go over there. Someone else.
I saw the earth for the first time Gris. I'd like to try.
Where is it?
Why?
Why? Why do you have to do it?
Three minutes is a lot of time for everyone to watch.
Excuse me.
Thank you for watching.
Sorry!
You're going to get a lot of tongue.
That's great. I'm doing Dizziness from the inside.
That's great, I'm looking forward to it.
I'm asking again, is there anything you'd like to pull out?
Any that, please.
Really, everyone, even those of you who are going through those adolescent years,
I'm sure there are people who are going through adolescence and people who have already grown up and still feel the same way,
I wonder if there is something in the film that will stick in the arms or pierce the hearts of many people,
We are also singing with a deep understanding of your beautiful words, which are filled with delicate feelings,
We sang the song with a lot of emotion, so please look forward to the music video as well,
I hope you enjoy the music video as well.
One minute to go.
Oh!
One minute to the end.
The end of the song.
I see.
What did he say?
Not yet.
What?
Dan!
I'm about to say it and have everyone stand by.
We've got 30 seconds left, and thank you all for your patience with the delivery.
We're sorry for any inconvenience this may have caused you, but we're having trouble with the infection.
I hope you enjoy the rest of the video.
So, let's go!
Booth Digence!
Mr. Dan.